RG 062:119, Town of Rocky Hill
Connecticut State Library
Town of Rocky Hill records
1819-1941
Connecticut State Library
Rocky Hill (Conn.)
7.5 cubic feet
Administrative, election, school and tax records for the town of Rocky Hill.
RG062_119
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Rocky Hill was incorporated in May 1843 and was taken from Wethersfield.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, school and tax records for the town of Rocky Hill.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Elections -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Statistics; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Statistics; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Rocky Hill -- Registers
Places:
Rocky Hill (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1819-1941
  - T000283
    - Election reports, voters lists, arraignment, resolutions at town meetings, calls for town meetings, 1845-1901 (Box Box 1)
    - Enrollment book, 1888-1901 (Box Box 1)
    - Enrollment list, 1861 (Box Box 1)
    - School returns, 1819-1841 (Box Box 2)
    - Reports of the Selectment and Treasurer, 1869-1894 (Box Box 2)
    - Individual tax list book, 1843 (Box Box 2)
    - Tax abstracts
      - 1848-1849, 1850, 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854-1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 3)
      - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 4)
      - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 5)
      - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889 (Box Box 6)
      - 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894 (Box Box 7)
      - 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 8)
      - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904 (Box Box 9)
      - 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1917 (Box Box 10)
  - 2006-002
    - Old age assistance, tax rate book, 1941; 1 volume